[{"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Other than don't get out (ph)?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "Talking to my favorite person.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "ORGAN: Can you quite believe you're in the green jacket, on CNN, you know, talking to the world about being Masters champion?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Yes, but can you believe it?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "We're friends forever.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Do you go and beat each other up the moment these interviews are over?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "The friendship?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What are the lessons?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "It's whoo.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "And performing and having hit records and touring and all that kind of thing, and all the press and the demands and the pressure, it is actually mentally and physically pretty exhausting, isn't it?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "-- you know?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "When \"Bridesmaids\" really popped and became this huge hit --", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Just celebrate what we're so lucky to be doing still?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "This is like the sort of thing you dream of, isn't it?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I feel like it has --", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "I mean, has it -- has it given you a completely new lease of life as a career?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I mean, I think the point is the kind of role model element of that film.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "And just because you were in a hit movie isn't necessarily going to guarantee that success, you know what I'm saying?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "For your kids, maybe?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "What -- the second time around, when you have all this success again now, people will say to me it's a lot sweeter, because when you stop it and it all goes away, and you watch other people enjoying all the highs and the good stuff, you kind of miss it, even though it's been painful a lot of the time and horrible and you fall out and everything, actually, a part of you really misses it.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "I just think it's that like edgy kind of \"Saturday Night Live,\" like just edgy, anything goes, women should do what they want and just have that edge, I don't know, you know?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Is it nice to be able to recapture it?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "We're back together.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Coming off.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "What is happening here?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I was just going to say --", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "-- for the way she's been battling this?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Because we eat for a reason, you know what I mean?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "It's a little strained at the moment.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "And how -- how is your relationship with your father now?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "There's peace.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Do you guys -- do you have one?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Yes, somewhat of a relationship.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "But is there actually what you would call a relationship?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Hmmm.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "How would you -- how would you describe it?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say that he's like a father figure so much.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "-- or is he like this sort of disjointed friend that you've got?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Well, because it's --", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Why did you play that?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Whoa.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "-- it's kind of perfect timing, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I just think that we need to spend more time with him.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Is he a better grandfather than father?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "They are hot.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "What is it like being with all those Baldwins?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Hysterical.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Are they funny to be around?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he's the oldest, so he thinks he knows what's right and what's the best thing to do.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Alec, he is -- is he the leader of the pack, or not really when they get together?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Several.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "No downsides?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Stephen?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes, go ahead.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Can I touch it?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "It feels nice.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "How does it feel?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "It's overwhelming.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "To be Bubba Watson right now?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Yes, for sure.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "But it's genuinely why, isn't it?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Yes, it has.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "It's been a quite extraordinary time for you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "The TV show.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Why did you want that car so much?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Talking to my favorite person.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Can you quite believe you're in the green jacket, on CNN, you know, talking to the world about being Masters champion?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "But can you believe it?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "No, I think the six-inch putt to win was the big moment.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "The difficulty of the shot and how it played out -- was that the moment for you?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I trust everything in -- every ounce of my body, I trust it all.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "What is it inside you that made you look down and say, I'm going for this?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "The moment when you had the six-inch putt to win the Masters, what goes through the golfer's mind when you're six inches away?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Right, exactly.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "ORGAN: Other than don't conk it out?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "I definitely wasn't thinking about this show.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Or is it all just focused on the shot?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "You weren't thinking of me when you won the Masters?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "The first thing that springs to mind is he told me I got two options: I can be a follower or a leader.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "How much of his son are you, do you think?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "ATSON: You know, I recognize that.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "How did you become so composed in such a pressurized moment, if the rest of the time you're all over the place?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Well, I think you got to learn from every situation.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "What lessons can you draw from that?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "Is he still the best you've seen, Tiger?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "\"America's Got Talent.\"", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "Bubba Watson, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "What were you doing there?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "Golf is boring.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "What was the thought process?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "I know who's not going to be a member.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 831, "question": "What are they going to do?", "qSentId": 830}, {"answer": "You.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "Who, me?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "Oh, for sure.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 879, "question": "Is she the great love of your life?", "qSentId": 878}, {"answer": "She said -- she didn't say much.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 892, "question": "What did she say to you when you became Masters champion?", "qSentId": 891}, {"answer": "Yes, and --", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 899, "question": "When he's old enough to focus?", "qSentId": 898}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 941, "question": "Did you make that yourself?", "qSentId": 940}, {"answer": "About nine feet.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 948, "question": "I don't know, how far is that, about five feet?", "qSentId": 947}, {"answer": "Yes, it could be.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 951, "question": "Oh, could be out of your range, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 950}, {"answer": "Don't you worry about me, mate.", "docId": "120414pmt", "aSentId": 961, "question": "What are you doing right now?", "qSentId": 960}]